Guide to the Stanford University, Asian American Activities Center, Records SC0487
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, 1973-2015; Accession ARCH-2016-032
  - Records
    - Taiwanese Culture Society, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Kayumanggi, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Pilipino American Student Union (PASU) 25th Anniversary, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Asian American Studies Paper by Valerie Mih, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Pilipino American Student Union (PASU) Yearbook, 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - CommunicAsians Magazine, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Sanskriti, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Asian American Theater Project (AATP) My Fair Lady, Yellow Face, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - STATIC Journal Winter, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Asian American Theater Project (AATP), undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Black and Yellow: Blasian Narratives, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Stanford Asian American Activism Committee (SAAAC), 2007 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Stanford Asian Pacific American Alumni Club (SAPAAC), undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Asian American Activities Center (A3C) Brochures, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Basmati Raas: Various Peformance Photos, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Korean Student Association (KSA) Spring Show: Reply, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Pilipino American Student Union (PASU) Pilipino Youth Leadership Conference PYLP: Bayanihan, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - I-Hotel, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Pilipino American Student Union, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Student Events, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Asian American Studies, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Asian American Theater Project (AATP): FOB, Goliath, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Monolid Magazine and other mags, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Japanese American Internee Reunion, 50th Anniversary of Exec Order 9066, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Listen to the Silence, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Asian Pacific American Policy Forum, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Reflections, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Reflections, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - From 9066 to 9/11: Community and Identity in Wartime America, 2005-2-10 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Service Across the Ethnic Community Centers: Resource Guide, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - A Brief History of International Students at Stanford, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - In Our Own Words: The Power of Aisan American Women's Voices - Alpha Kappa Delta Phi, 2002-3-2 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Early Asian American Activities Center (A3C)/Volunteer Student Organizations (VSOs), undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Struggle for Asian Americans, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Asian American Activities Center (A3C) Budget Cuts, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Pubs and Programs, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Audio
    - KZSU Radio A Grain of Sand: The Stanford Asian American Process Through Radio, 1974-1975; 6 audiocassette(s)
  - Posters
    - Tule Lake Pilgrimage, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Asian Pacific Student Union: State Wide Conference, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Chinatown Committee to Celebrate International Women's Day, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Anti-Asian Graffiti Canvas, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Asian Americans for Black Lives Matter, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Music in Conversation, 2014-5-9 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Maxine Hong Kingston: From Woman Warrior to Book of Peace, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - California and Beyond, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - 3 Asian American Theater Project (AATP) Posters: R&L (Signed Production), undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Asian American Theater Project (AATP) R&L Production, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Walking Backwards with Shirley Geok-Lin Lim: Poetics and Life Writing, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Asian-Pacific American Heritage Week, 1980-5-7-1980-5-14 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Stanford University Asian and Pacific Islander (API) Heritage Month, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Hito Hata: Raise the Banner, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Asian Amrican Theater Project (AATP): My Fair Lady, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Listen to the Silence, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Nidhi Chanani, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Listen to the Silence: JR Aquino and the Company (Signed), 2014 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Listen to the Silence: JR Aquino and the Company (Not Signed), 2014 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Saving face: How a Geek Became a Filmaker Alice Wu's '90 MA '92, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Asian American Performing Arts Series, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Asian America This is Our Home, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Listen to the Silence, Can't Stop Won't Stop: Sustaining the Asian American Movement, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Dalit Women's Self Respect Project, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Sweat Free Stanford Banner, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Stanford Asian American Activism Committee (SAAAC) "Another 4 Years" rally banner, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Listen to the Silence Sam Tsui Signed, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Asian and Pacific Island (API) Heritage Month, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Asian Pacific Islander Hertiage Month, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Videorecordings, Accession ARCH-2017-161
  - Origins Panel, Reunion, 2009; SC0487_2016-148_01; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 1)
  - Origins Panel, Reunion, 2009; SC0487_2016-148_02; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 1)
  - Origins, 2009; SC0487_2016-148_03; 1 videotape(s) (minidv) (Box 1)
- "Stanford Asians" film, Accession ARCH-2017-294
  - Stanford Asians, 2017
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2018-013
  - AASA memoranda, minutes, correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Asian American Women's Journal, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sourcebooks (1 of 2), 1974-2013 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sourcebooks (2 of 2), 1974-2013 (Box 1, Folder 4)